So let's get started with that course.
Bu yzden o dersten balayalm.
But first I want to explain you how you can get the most out of this course.
Ancak nce bu dersten en iyi ekilde nasl yararlanabileceinizi aklamak istiyorum.
Obviously you watch the videos and I highly recommend that you all to code along right.
Belli ki videolar izliyorsunuz ve hepinizin sadan kodlamasn neriyorum.
Decode yourself.
zn kendiniz.
This is how you learn the most.
En ok nasl rendiiniz budur.
Additionally check my source code.
Ayrca kaynak kodumu kontrol edin.
If you are encountering issues you can find it attached to the end of each module and also to a lot
nk bazen sadece kk bir yanl yazlm ve kaynam altrmazsanz kodunuzu yazp
of lectures for all the module and I do provide the source code because sometimes it's just a tiny typo
sizinle karlatrn, kodunuzda neyin yanl olduunu renemez ve neden yanl gittiini daha iyi anlarsnz.
and if you don't run my source code and compare it to yours you won't be able to find out what's wrong
Sorunlarla karlayorsanz, her bir modln sonuna eklediklerini ve ayrca tm modl
in your code and get a deeper understanding of why it went wrong.
iin birok konferansa katlandn grebilir ve kaynak kodu salarsnz,
Also consider D many hints and things.
Ayrca, D birok ipucu ve eyi dnn.
I will teach you in the debugging section of this course.
Bu dersin hata ayklama blmnde size reteceim.
There I will teach you how to handle re-act errors and how to react to them and fix them.
Burada, yeniden ileme hatalarn nasl ele alacanz ve onlara nasl tepki vereceinizi ve onaracam reteceim.
Definitely something you have to know how to do.
Kesinlikle, nasl yaplacan bilmeniz gereken bir ey.
So use that knowledge you gain there to fix any issues you encounter.
Karlatnz sorunlar dzeltmek iin orada kazandnz bilgiyi kullann.
Now if you're stuck and you can't find error ask in the Q and A section.
imdi taklp kaldysanz ve hata bulamyorsanz Q ve A blmnde sorun.
My team and I are more than happy to help you there but that's important.
Ekibimle birlikte size yardmc olmaktan ok mutluyuz, ancak bu nemli.
Don't just ask there.
Sadece orada sorma.
Also answered there.
Ayrca orada cevaplad.
I'm not saying this because I don't want to answer your questions.
Bunu sylemiyorum nk sorularnza cevap vermek istemiyorum.
I will but if you answer you'll learn way more than if you ask.
steyeceim ama cevap vereceksen daha fazla reneceksin.
Asking is so simple but answering is hard.
Sormak ok basit, ancak cevap vermek zor.
And you can't go wrong there.
Ve orada yanl gidemem.
Even if your answer is wrong no one is going to kill you.
Cevabnz yanl olsa bile sizi kimse ldrecek deil.
Instead you're going to learn if people correct you and answering forces you to think about a problem
Bunun yerine, insanlar sizi dzeltip uyarlamayacaklarn ve cevaplama gleriyle bir problemi dnp zm
and find a solution.
bulup bulamayacanz reneceksiniz.
If you really want to become a great re-act developer you have to solve problems and answering the Q
Gerekten harika bir yeniden-aktr gelitirici olmak istiyorsanz, problemleri zmeniz ve Q ve A blmne
and A section is a good way of practicing just that and finally practice practice practice.
cevap vermeniz sadece bunu uygulamak iin iyi bir yoldur ve en sonunda uygulama pratiklerini uygulamaktr.
It's as easy as that.
O kadar kolay.
Even after you've finished this course you've got to practice the things you've learned.
Bu dersi bitirdikten sonra bile rendiiniz eyleri uygulamaya koymanz gerekiyor.
You have to build your own demo projects set your own challenges Dudi exercises from this course alter
Kendi demo projelerinizi kurmanz gerekir kendi zorluklarnz belirleyebilirsiniz. Bu ders Dudi egzersizlerini
the code you'll learn in this course practice react.
deitirir; bu ders pratikte tepki gsterecektir.
If you follow these steps and follow through this entire course you'll be an awesome re-act developer
Bu admlar izlerseniz ve bu tm dersi takip ederseniz harika bir yeniden davranm gelitiricisi
and you'll be able to apply for chops.
olacaksnz ve pirzola bavurusunda bulunabileceksiniz.
Become a re-act freelancer whatever you want with dad.
Babanzla ne yaparsanz yapn, re-act freelancer olunuz.
Let's dive into react and learn how it works.
Hadi reaksiyona girip nasl altn renelim.